(Sheldon:)Leonard would never
go swimming in public
(Sheldon:)without his swim shirt.
(Amy:)I'm sure he brought it.
(Sheldon:)No, but last year,
at Magic Mountain,
(Sheldon:)he got such a bad sunburn,
(Sheldon:)we had to cut him out of it.
(Amy:)He probably got a new one.
Finish your breakfast.
(Amy:)Look, there's an entire
section of my dashboard
(Amy:)that doesn't have
any syrup on it.
(Sheldon:)You're acting odd. Why?
(Amy:)I'm odd all the time,
everyone knows that.
(Amy:)Just last night,
(Amy:)I tried to see how many fava
beans I could fit in my mouth.
(Sheldon:)Tell me the truth.
28.
Come on.
Fifty-six.
Amy!
(Sheldon:)What's going on?
(Amy:)All right.
(Amy:)Don't get upset, but...
(Amy:)an earlier appointment
opened up for Leonard
(Amy:)and he's getting
the surgery right now.
(Sheldon:)I see.